[{"answer": "Don't call him a dipshit", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And you don't.  What's she doing in there", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Finding the real world to your liking, Mr. my friend", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Back? Were you ever really here", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " You could grace our hallowed halls again, if, while you're here, you make a sincere effort to be part of our little school community", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How would you do that, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Like what? The moons of Jupiter", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't want to have any conversation", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " You're like this fly, buzzing buzzing everywhere", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " This play", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Fire is like a living thing. Wild. Unpredictable", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No. Not like you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He's a softy. Got him wrapped around my finger", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Know so", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Sometimes I come here and just scan the heavens", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Looking for something. someone", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "The Bible. Why should I read a bunch of dumb stories about some ancient guy who supposedly worked miracles", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Your father doesn't like me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " 'Then why don't you talk to her?", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " 'She'll sure think the same if I do it. You're her father and comes a time when a father's gotta mention.", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Okay. Maybe some of that is true", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't want to be just your friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You don't know the first thing about being someone's friend", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You don't know what you want", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Getting out won't be your problem. It'll be figuring out what you want when you get somewhere.", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " It means you can do anything", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It was a play", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I have expectations, too", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "New paint. Extra chrome. Not a scratch anywhere", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Reconditioned. Completely. Be a collector's someday. Twelve hundred", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Where did you get", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I didn't say you did", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " She great or what", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No.  But are you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I care for her", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I wouldn't do tha", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It's places like this that make me certain there's a God", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm sure. Pretty sure", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Where's the one you're building", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Wait, back up. You lied", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "We didn't tell him any different for year", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Since I was five. My mom's a cocktail waitress", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You and the Carter boy. Want to catch me up on recent developments", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm asking how much", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Maybe. But that's not the real reason. You think if I tell, he'll disappear and that's what you want! Me all to yourself", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "This, him, my friend, is what's best for me", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " No you didn't.  But he did change. Just not enough", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " I am mad at you! And at that place! And the universe! And God!  I don't even know where to put all my anger", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I should have told you sooner", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "No. The drugs just stopped working. If anything, doing things I love kept me healthy longer", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You have a key", "docId": "awalktoremember.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I've talked to your father", "qsentId": 52}]